- Mr. Ahn! - Mr. Ahn!
Please say something.
I have somehing to say about the great lawyer Ahn Do Hoon.
- Please make a comment. - Stop! Stop it!
- That's enough. - What?
San... Don't you want to see him?
San... Your son. Don't you miss him?
How dare you! How dare you mention his name?
If he's alive,
how come I don't even know about it.
How can you take San as an excuse?
I did it for you and Do Hoon.
He's alive. Trust me.
You need to care about yourselves.
How could you live as a single mom
and an ex-convict?
You and Do Hoon weren't meant to be together.
How can you take care of a boy that was born in jail?
You protect your son in that way,
how can you do this to my son?
So what if he was born in jail?
So what if I'm an ex-convict?
I can't raise him by my own?
What if his father's a murderer?
Bring him to me.
Where is San? Where is he?
Bring him back to me! Bring him back to me!
Why? Why?
It's cold.
Long time no see. You must attend the meeting this time.
Mom.
- Mom. - What's she doing?
Hey! What are you doing to my son?
Jung Hwan, are you okay?
San.
His name is San.
- Jung Hwan, let's go. - He's San.
What are you doing?
Let me go.
Yoo Jung!
Look at him.
Look what you've taken away from me.
I didn't know. Trust me.
Don't say that you didn't know.
You could've found out.
When you heard that San was dead,
you didn't even see the body.
Why didn't you go to see him?
While your mother was doing this,
you just pretend knowing nothing.
How can you say you didn't know? How can you?
Ja Yeong. San didn't recognize me.
How could he not recognize his own mother?
How is it possible?
I need to get him back.
I'll get him back.
Sure. You gave birth to him and breastfed him.
You should get him back. That bastard.
Ja Yeong! Where are you going?
What are you going to do? Beat them up?
It might make you feel better,
but it won't help Yoo Jung.
Hae Ri, don't just stand there.
Go get some water.
Do you remember that old lady
who was in the next room when we were in jail?
She's an expert in fabricating documents.
She knows a lot of techinicians in this field.
Let's contact her.
We can find out who forged
San's death certificate.
Let's find that bastard.
How could you do that?
How could you do such a thing to her?
- I did it for Do Hoon. - Stop!
You only think about Do Hoon.
That's why Do Hoon ended up like this.
What should I do? How can I face Yoo Jung?
What have you done?
We have his death certificate.
Do you know what you've done?
Well... A friend who I met in the sauna,
- said her niece doesn't have a baby. - Mother.
I did it for you.
I didn't do it for me.
Do you think it was easy for me?
How could you raise him at that moment?
Why not send him to a good family?
Excuse me.
We're from the police station.
What's going on?
Well... Ms. Park Gyeok.
Park Gyeok. You know who Mr. Lee Sangcheol is.
Mr. Lee said that you paid him 3 million KRW,
to fabricate a document. Is that true?
The victim reported it to the police.
Anyway, we're arresting you for fabricating a document and using it.
Wait! Even if it's true, this is her first offense.
Can you investigate without detaining her?
I'm his grandmother.
I did it for everybody.
I didn't mean to do this.
Everyone has his own reasons.
You have to come with me anyway.
Wait!
- Do Hoon! Do Hoon!
- Honey! Honey! - Dear! Dear!
- Detective! Dear! Dear! - Do Hoon! Do Hoon!
Are you just going to let her go like that?
Do something about it.
What can I do?
Dear! Dear!
What? What is it?
What is it?
You want to say something. Say it!
- Ms. Kang's son is alive. - What?
Mrs. Park Gyeok.
Someone is here for you.
In order to get rid of me,
you said San was dead.
Now you tell me that San isn't dead,
do you think I'd be grateful
and forgive Do Hoon at once?
That was the best choice at that time.
You were so young at that time.
Suffer the same thing
as my father did.
I want you to see Do Hoon wither away in jail.
Just imagine it.
Yoo Jung, Do Hoon didn't do anything wrong. I did everything.
If your son is so precious to you,
how could you do that to me?
They're taking good care of San.
I visit them every month.
They let me have dinner with San, and said I'm his grandma.
They are good people.
What about me? Don't you think I would've done the same?
I want you to know how painful it is
not to be able to see your son even when he is alive.
Just experience it yourself.
Yoo Jung!
Yoo Jung! Yoo Jung!
Please.
Don't take Jung Hwan away from me.
I never abandoned San.
If I'd known that his birth mother was alive,
I would've come to you.
When he was old enough to understand...
I was going to tell him what really happened.
I didn't mean to lie to him.
He's not old enough to understand.
It's not too late.
No!
I can't let him go.
No...
I can't give up Jung Hwan. Please!
I can't give up either.
I can't give up San.
No.
Stop drinking.
Are you trying to kill yourself again?
Right. If I died at that time,
I wouldn't have to see you become such a person today.
Mom will be released soon.
This is her first offence. She'll just be fined.
Unbelievable!
How can you and your mother be so cruel?
That's because you're too weak.
That's right. It's all my fault.
You're right.
Gwang Min!
What are you doing? Your father is waiting for him.
No, I need to see him first.
Min Joo.
We haven't celebrated your birthday.
Come here. I've got presents for you.
Look!
Is this your present?
I heard that you liked it. Don't you?
I do.
That's great.
I went to find my father with Kwang Soo in winter.
We couldn't find him, and we were hungry.
While I was crying like a baby,
your father came and bought us some noodles.
It was so delicious.
What's this?
Wait. I'll prepare something for you to eat.
He said he wanted to eat this.
Just care about your daughter.
You said I'm too fat, you don't even want me to eat.
You should lose another 2kg.
Do you want to look fat in your graduation photo?
Min Joo, don't eat those noodles.
Gwang Min, she's like a stepmother to me.
Why are you looking at me like this?
Let it go. I already know.
I've known since middle school.
You've known all along?
Yes.
When I tell her that she acts like a stepmother,
She looks like the heroine in the tragedy.
She's pretty at that time.
And she'll treat me better.
I was angry in the beginning,
but she's still my mother, right?
He had a blanket with the moon and stars on it.
Wait.
Here.
When he first came here, he couldn't sleep without it.
It's too old.
Can I take it with me?
I'm home.
Jung Hwan, why are you so early?
Does your stomach hurt again?
If you're sick like this, mommy...
Mommy will hurt as well.
Mommy will hurt as well?
Who is she?
Mommy, why are you crying?
Are you felling uncomfortable?
Why?
Did she hurt you?
No, it's me.
She didn't do anything wrong.
I think she did. Should I tell her to leave?
The trial is set for next week.
I'll see you then.
I made it for him,
but he can sleep well without it now.
He's allergic to crab meat.
If he's not happy, he'll tear up paper.
He rides a bike with his father on weekends.
Did you know?
Yoo Jung.
I didn't know any of that. He's my son.
He's my San.
I don't know what he likes, how he grew up.
I don't know anything.
What should I do?
You still don't know?
Aren't you coming home again tonight?
I'm thinking about the painting to sen to Hannam-dong.
You know how picky she is.
Don't run the gallery anymore.
Buying and selling paintings isn't for you.
It's my job. What else can I do?
I think you look the hapiest when you paint.
I'm busy. Can you leave?
Se Yeon.
When I was devastated,
is this how you felt?
I want to do something for you, but I don't know what to do.
I hope you can be happy again.
You and I were happy together.
Not knowing that all the other kids hated us,
We were hanging out together,
and we were happy at that time, right?
Stop!
I'm trying hard not to like you.
Please stop.
I'm sorry.
Are you happy to play outside?
- Are you happy? - Yes.
Mommy made these rolls.
Aren't they good?
This one?
- Isn't it delicious? - Yes.
It's the best, right?
Jung Hwan.
Madam. You're here again.
Don't call me madam.
I'm your auntie.
I'm your mommy's friend.
Go and play.
See you next time.
Jung Hwan.
Go.
Daddy, I want to ride my bike.
Sure.
Let's go.
Hold on tight.
Here we go.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Look what you've taken away from me.
Look what you've been missing in your life.
So good! So good!
- After throwing away something precious, -Fighting!
Look what happened to us.
Look at it yourself.
I'm sorry, Yoo Jung.
It's all my fault. Sorry.
Yoo Jung. Sorry. Sorry.
It's all my fault.
Sorry. Sorry.
Idiot! Idiot! How can you abandon San?
How are you going to live?
Ja Yeong, I didn't abandon him.
I don't have to live with him simply because I'm his mother.
If San is happy, that's all that matters.
San looked so happy when he smiled.
This is crazy. I don't know.
If someone took my son away like that,
I'd chase them down to the end of the world.
I thought I'd do the same.
But I couldn't.
After they took San away from me,
it hurts so much I thought I'd die.
I couldn't do it.
When San first went to her place...
He didn't stop crying.
He didn't eat for a week
while looking for me.
He kept on crying.
I couldn't possibly bring him back.
What if he cried all day saying
that he missed his mommy?
I guess I was wrong about myself.
I thought I'd be okay even if you didn't love me.
But I'm not okay.
Let's end this.
Se Yeon.
Min Hyuk!
Don't worry about me.
I'm Shin Se Yeon.
You're giving your shares to Se Yeon?
You two broke up and you want to give your shares to her?
I'm leaving them not to Se Yeon,
but to the Shina Foundation.
I guess she'll use it wisely.
Are you out of your mind?
I'll give up my management right.
Min Hyuk.
Don't make a rash decision.
It's not a rash decision.
It's a reasonable one.
You're better than me.
I'm saying this, not as your son, but for the K Corporation.
So,
you still want to be with that girl?
No.
I'd love to be with her,
but I'm too ashamed.
Ashamed?
Everybody makes mistakes.
It's important how you make up for them.
That's what she said.
I
want to make up for what I did.
What?
The most impoverished place.
The place where no one wants to go.
Send me there.
I'll work hard.
No.
I haven't paid off my debt, yet.
Take it.
If not, he'll be angry with me.
You can pay your debt later.
Bit by bit.
He can get through
only when he hears from you.
He
is leaving for Armenia today.
Is he leaving so soon?
He won't be back for a while.
Hey!
What's going on?
I'm going to close up the gallery, and leave.
I want to see you before I leave.
I guess you've heard about what I've done.
You still want to see me after knowing that?
I'll be prosecuted next week.
It was me who killed Seo Ji Hee,
not me.
That's why I want to see you.
I thought I should tell you this.
You didn't kill Ms. Seo Ji Hee. It was me.
I told President Jo that I'd marry Min Hyuk.
You and Min Hyuk have to end up like this.
I'm pregnant.
We'll have a baby after our marriage.
Hey!
Do you think Min Hyuk's father will approve of that baby?
Do you think he'll let you give birth to the baby?
Take it.
Min Hyuk's father doesn't know that you're pregnant.
Should I go tell him now?
Disappear.
Disappear from Min Hyuk's life forever.
This is my last warning.
Next time, it won't be a warning.
I didn't think she'd actually die.
I wished she were dead.
That's what I wished for.
I thought I'd be happy if I could be with Min Hyuk.
I guess Min Hyuk and I weren't meant to be together.
Sorry.
You happened to be involved to this
in the wrong place at the wrong time.
I've thought about why things turned out like this
over and over again.
If only I hadn't been there.
If only it hadn't been raining.
If only the truck hadn't appeared.
I was so angry.
I was angry at what happened to me,
I was afraid everything I built up would collapse.
Now I've lost Yoo Jung,
my son.
I've lost them forever.
Do Hoon!
I killed Seo Ji Hee.
It's my fault.
Thank you for everything.
Have a nice trip.
I heard...
You didn't release
the Shina Foundation files even till now.
Thank you.
I'm going to miss
your paintings.
Did you admit that you abandoned Mr. Kang Woo Chul last month?
Yes.
The hit-and-run case from four years ago.
Do you admit that you were driving,
instead of Ms. Kang who's already served time?
I'm asking if you admit
that you're responsible for Ms. Seo Ji Hee's death?
Father, can I use your car today?
Why do you use the car today?
Do you have to go somewhere far?
I have something to do.
Right, if you don't want to be late, you need a car.
Try to be nice this time.
If you ruin it again...
Mom, I'm late. I have to go.
Do Hoon! Do Hoon!
Have a bite! Come on.
See you.
Take care, prosecutor!
By the way...
Did you fix the wiper?
The weather forecast said it won't rain today.
You never worry about anything.
I'm going to finish his leftovers.
Why aren't they working?
They're not?
That's strange.
Stay inside, okay?
Okay.
Yes.
Yes, I'm almost there.
Min Hyuk went to see that girl.
Bring her back.
I love you.
Do Hoon!
I told you to stay inside.
What was it?
Thank god. I was so worried.
Let's go.
Wait.
Let me move it. Other cars might hit it.
Over here, over here.
One, two, three.
Okay.
Go.
Defendant.
Do you plead guilty?
I do.
You look great.
When did you get back?
At dawn.
Is everything ready?
You're not going to regret it?
No. I'll not regret.
Gwang Min.
Min Joo.
Hey!
It's getting late. Let's go.
Okay.
What's going on?
They've been dating while you are abrod..
What's this?
I'll be right there.
So...
Kwang Soo!
I saw Congressman Shin's wife at the boutique yesterday, and she didn't look good.
Congressman Shin isn't going to run for President this time?
Who knows?
Politicians tend to repeat the same mistakes when the situation turns better.
You're not going to go?
It's the inauguration.
Gwang Min will take care of it.
You said you'd consider him as your son.
I guess it's not true.
Do you still want Minyeok to have it?
Min Hyuk has tried his best.
Let him do what he really wants to do.
Mr. Choi...
C.E.O. Choi will do just fine.
Min Hyuk is your only son,
but, what should we do about Min Joo?
Gwang Min's too old for her.
She's insisting on marrying him.
She's just like you.
Sorry?
We've lived for 20 years together.
Your letter.
What is it? You've got a letter.
Pizza buns!
When is your coffee shop going to open?
I'm not ready yet. We have to wait till next month.
I'll sell the coffee.
I've been taking classes to become a barista for that coffee shop.
And you're taking this as an excues not to pay your rent.
Where is Sandra?
Congratulations
Where is Alex?
Is he a pet?
How can you call him like that?
Alex invited you all.
He'll cook a lot of delicious food for you.
Wow, you look prettier with straight hair.
You should've done it earlier.
So what?
Someonw said I would be pretty if I straighten my hair,
but he's now dating with Hae Ri.
Hello.
Speak of the devil.
Hello, Kwang Soo.
What does Alex like?
Streusel bread?
Give me that one, too.
Yummy yummy
It's tasty.
Is the baby coming?
Is the baby coming? Is the baby coming?
What should we do?
- Hospital! Hospital! - What should we do?
- Take her to the hospital. - Kwang Soo!
Oh my god.
Go drive the car.
It's okay. It's okay.
I'll be right there.
Okay.
It's too sweet. I don't like sweet stuff.
I'm not here to see you. I'm here to ask you something.
You made a wish at the pagoda.
What did you wish for?
It's a secret.
This is almost over. No more secrets.
If I tell you the secret, it's not funny.
You like funny stuff.
It's not funny.
I want to know. Just tell me.
No.
Why not?
I'll keep it secret so that you'll keep following me around, sir.
I'm not the C.E.O. anymore.
Really?
Call my name instead of sir.
You still owe me.
Do as I say. Call me by my name.
Min Hyuk.
Again.